<?xml version = "1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="iDiarySS.xsl"?>

<idiary>
   <entry>
      <date>19 September 2011</date>
      <cool><title>The Digital Diary</title>
          This will be fun! I start my digital journal today. So, to launch it with the right sentiment,
          I looked up what Henry David Thoreau wrote on the first day of his famous <ital>Journal.</ital> He said,
          <quote>"'What are you doing now?' he asked. 'Do you keep a journal?' So I make my first entry today."</quote>
          Which, I guess, is pretty much what I just said. Great minds ... !
      </cool>           
   </entry>
   
   <entry>
    <date>20 September 2011</date>
    <cool>
       <title>Kepler-16b, <ital>Star Wars</ital> Planet</title>
         NASA found Tatooine! It's a planet orbiting a binary star system, just like Tatooine in the <ital>Star Wars</ital>
         movies. It's only 200 lightyears away -- Let's Go!!! -- and is about the size of Saturn. According to Slate's 
       <link url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R8KkHBqO4kk" > <ital>Trending</ital>  </link>Report, the two stars 
         orbit each other every 41 days, and the Kepler-16b planet orbits them once every 229 days. 
         <nasavid url="http://www.youtube.com/embed/0MfRo0eC1ks" />
         This is today's Astronomy Picture of the Day, <link url="http:apod.nasa.gov"> APOD, </link>which is one of
         my all time favorite Web sites.
    </cool>
   </entry>
   
   <entry>
     <date> 21 September 2011 </date>
     <cool>
        OMG! There are 0 rats in Alberta, Canada! Really?! It's bigger than France! I guess it's true, because
        <link url="http://www1.agric.gov.ab.ca/$department/deptdocs.nsf/all/agdex3441">here's the story.</link>
        Was <ital>Ratatouille</ital> allowed in the theaters???
     </cool>
   </entry>
   
   <entry>
     <date> 22 September 2011</date>
       <cool>I ran across this today, and am saving it here so I don't lose track of it. I don't quite get it! 
        <poem>

           <p_title>Selecting a Reader</p_title>
           <poet>Ted Kooser</poet>
           <line>First, I would have her be beautiful,</line>
           <line>and walking carefully up on my poetry</line>
           <line>at the loneliest moment of an afternoon,</line>
           <line>her hair still damp at the neck</line>

           <line>from washing it. She should be wearing</line>
           <line>a raincoat, an old one, dirty</line>
           <line>from not having money enough for the cleaners.</line>
           <line>She will take out her glasses, and there</line>
           <line>in the bookstore, she will thumb</line>
           <line>over my poems, then put the book back</line>

           <line>up on its shelf. She will say to herself,</line>
           <line>"For that kind of money, I can get</line>
           <line>my raincoat cleaned." And she will.</line>
        </poem>
        
       </cool>
   </entry>
   
   <entry>
     <date> 23 September 2011</date>
     <cool>
     <title>One Woman Achieves Immortality!</title>
         I just finished reading <ital>The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks</ital> by Rebecca Skloot. Lacks was a 
         poor African American tobacco farmer who had five children, and died in 1951 at age 31 from cervical
         cancer. Doctors at Johns Hopkins took cancer cells from her without her permission. The cells had a
         never-before-seen ability to continue to live in a culture medium. Most cells die after a few generations but hers
         are still going today, 60 years later! They have been critical to a huge amount of medical research.
         It is a terrific book! <para>
         <pic file="pix/lacks.jpg" width = "120"/> <pic file="pix/hela.jpg" width="350"/></para>
         The cells are known as HELA cells, the first two letters of her two names, and they hit on Google more 
         than 2 million times.
     </cool>
   </entry>
   
</idiary>

